[
  {
    "id": 1,
    "prompt": "Mountain Dew was originally slang for:",
    "choices": [
      "Coffee",
      "Red Bull",
      "Whiskey",
      "Moonshine"
    ],
    "answer": "Moonshine",
    "links": [
      {
        "href": "www.google.com",
        "text": "LMGTFY"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "prompt": "What is the scientific name of the common potato?:",
    "choices": [
      "Solanum tuberosum L.",
      "Mr. Potato",
      "Potato otatop",
      "Mrs. Potato"
    ],
    "answer": "Solanum tuberosum L.",
    "links": [
      {
        "href": "www.google.com",
        "text": "LMGTFY"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "prompt": "Who was the first woman pilot to fly solo across the Atlantic?:",
    "choices": [
      "Susan B. Anthony",
      "Beyonce",
      "Amelia Earhart",
      "Hew Keller"
    ],
    "answer": "Amelia Earhart",
    "links": [
      {
        "href": "www.google.com",
        "text": "LMGTFY"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "prompt": "The Hoover Dam in the United States is built on what river?",
    "choices": [
      "North Carolina River",
      "The Colorado River",
      "Yadkin River",
      "Hoover River"
    ],
    "answer": "The Colorado River",
    "links": [
      {
        "href": "www.google.com",
        "text": "LMGTFY"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "prompt": "Which liquor is made from the blue agave plant?",
    "choices": [
      "Coffee",
      "Tequila",
      "Whiskey",
      "Moonshine"
    ],
    "answer": "Tequila",
    "links": [
      {
        "href": "www.google.com",
        "text": "LMGTFY"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "prompt": "Steve Jobs, Steve Wozniak, and Ronald Wayne founded what company in 1976?",
    "choices": [
      "Nintendo",
      "Sony",
      "Microsoft",
      "Apple Computer, Inc."
    ],
    "answer": "Apple Computer, Inc.",
    "links": [
      {
        "href": "www.google.com",
        "text": "LMGTFY"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "prompt": "How many feet are in a mile?",
    "choices": [
      "5280",
      "328",
      "1020",
      "About 200"
    ],
    "answer": "5280",
    "links": [
      {
        "href": "www.google.com",
        "text": "LMGTFY"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "prompt": "Quasimodo is a fictional character from what novel?",
    "choices": [
      "The Hunchback of Notre-Dam",
      "Harry Potter",
      "Goosebumps",
      "I don't read"
    ],
    "answer": "The Hunchback of Notre-Dam",
    "links": [
      {
        "href": "www.google.com",
        "text": "LMGTFY"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "prompt": "All of these are examples of ORMs except?",
    "choices": [
      "Express",
      "Sequelize",
      "A custom library taking callbacks",
      "Mongoose"
    ],
    "answer": "Express",
    "links": [
      {
        "href": "www.google.com",
        "text": "LMGTFY"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "prompt": "In humans, what is the only internal organ capable of regenerating lost tissue?",
    "choices": [
      "Heart",
      "Bladder",
      "Kidney",
      "Liver"
    ],
    "answer": "Liver",
    "links": [
      {
        "href": "www.google.com",
        "text": "LMGTFY"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 11,
    "prompt": "Which of these REST actions is *mismatched* to its CRUD verb?",
    "choices": [
      "CREATE - INSERT",
      "GET - SELECT",
      "PATCH - UPDATE",
      "DESTROY - DELETE"
    ],
    "answer": "CREATE - INSERT",
    "links": [
      {
        "href": "www.google.com",
        "text": "LMGTFY"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 13,
    "prompt": "What dog breed is half-dog tall and a dog-and-a-half long?",
    "choices": [
      "German Sheperd",
      "CatDog",
      "Dachshund",
      "Labrador"
    ],
    "answer": "Dachshund",
    "links": [
      {
        "href": "www.google.com",
        "text": "LMGTFY"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 15,
    "prompt": "How could you make n^2 better",
    "choices": [
      "Grow a tree",
      "Use nlogn by implementing a tree",
      "n^3",
      "n^4"
    ],
    "answer": "Use nlogn by implementing a tree",
    "links": [
      {
        "href": "www.google.com",
        "text": "LMGTFY"
      }
    ]
  }
]